stripclublist.com 2019-03-31

# Strip Club List - Club Owner

Last Updated: February 2017

Our Services instantly connect people everywhere to what’s most meaningful to them. For example, any registered user of SCN can post a comment, which is public by default, and can include a message of 140 characters or less and content like photos, videos, and links to other websites.

What you share on SCN may be viewed all around the world instantly.

This Privacy Policy describes how and when we collect, use and share your information across our websites, SMS, APIs, email notifications, applications, buttons, widgets, ads, commerce services, that link to this Policy (collectively, the “Services”), and from our partners and other third parties. For example, you send us information when you use our Services on the web, via SMS, or from an application such as SCN for Mac, SCN for Android. When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, storage, disclosure, and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. This includes any information you choose to provide that is deemed sensitive under applicable law.

Irrespective of which country you live in, you authorize us to post, transfer, store, and use your information in the United States and any other countries where we operate. In some of these countries, the privacy and data protection laws and rules regarding when government authorities may access data may vary from those in the country where you live.

## Information Collection and Use

**Basic Account Information:** If you choose to create a SCN account, you must provide us with some personal information, such as your name, username, password, email address, or phone number. On SCN, your name and username are listed publicly, including on your profile page and in search results, and you can use either your real name or a pseudonym. You can create and manage multiple SCN accounts, the contact information you provide to log in is not public. Some of our product features, such as searching and viewing public SCN user profiles or watching a Periscope broadcast on SCN, do not require you to create an account.

**Contact Information:** You may use your contact information, such as your email address or phone number, to customize your account or enable certain account features, for example If you provide us with your phone number, you agree to receive text messages to that number from us. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services, to market to you, to help prevent spam, fraud, or abuse, and to help others find your account, including through third-party services and client applications. You may use your setting to control notifications you receive from SCN. You may also unsubscribe from a notification by following the instructions contained within the notification or the instructions on our website. You control whether others can find you on SCN by your email address or phone number.

**Additional Information:** You may choose to provide us with additional information to help improve and personalize your experience across our Services. For example, you may choose to upload and sync your address book so that we can help you find and connect with users you know or help other users find and connect with you. We may later tailor content, such as making suggestions or showing user accounts and SCNs for you and other users, based on imported address book contacts. You can delete your imported address book contacts at any time by visiting your Contacts Dashboard in your privacy settings. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. If you connect your account on our Services to your account on another service in order to cross-post between our Services and that service, the other service may send us your registration or profile information on that service and other information that you authorize. This information enables cross-posting, helps us improve the Services, and is deleted from our Services within a few weeks of your disconnecting from our Services your account on the other service.

SCN is primarily designed to help you share information with the world. Most of the information you provide us through SCN is information you are asking us to make public. You may provide us with profile information to make public on SCN, such as a short biography, your location, your website, date of birth, video or a picture. Additionally, your public information includes the messages you send and the metadata provided such as when the client application you used information about your account, such as creation time, language, country, and time zone; and the lists you create, people you follow you. SCN broadly and instantly disseminates your public information to a wide range of users, customers, and services, including search engines, developers, and publishers that integrate SCN content into their services, and organizations such as universities, public health agencies, and market research firms that analyze the information for trends and insights. When you share information or content like photos, videos, and links via the Services, you should think carefully about what you are making public. We may use this information to make inferences, like what topics you may be interested in. Our default is almost always to make the information you provide through the Services public for as long as you do not delete it, but we generally make the information more private if you want. For certain profile information fields we provide you to select who can see this information in your profile. If you provide us with profile information and you don’t see a visibility setting, that information is public. You can change the language associated with your account at any time using your account settings, available within your dashboard.

We provide certain features that allow you to communicate more privately. For example, you can use Direct Messages to have private conversations with other SCN users. When you privately communicate with others through our Services, such as by sending and receiving Direct Messages, we will store and process your communications, and information related to them. Please note that if you interact with public SCN content shared with you via Direct Message, for instance by liking a message shared via Direct Message, those interactions may be public. While features like Direct Messages are intended to be private, please remember that recipients may copy, store, and re-share the contents of your communications.

**Location Information:** We may receive information about your location. For example, you may choose to publish your location in your SCNs and in your SCN profile. You may also tell us your location when you set your trend location on SCN.com. We may also determine location by using other data from your device, such as precise location information from GPS, information about wireless networks or cell towers near your mobile device, or your IP address. We may use and store information about your location to provide features of our Services, such as SCNing with your location, and to improve and customize the Services, for example, with more relevant content like local trends, stories, ads, and suggestions for people to follow.

**Commerce Services:** You may provide your payment information, including your credit or debit card number, card expiration date, CVV code, and billing address (collectively, “Payment Information”), along with your shipping address, to complete a commerce transaction through our Services. To facilitate future purchases, we store your Payment Information (excluding CVV code) and shipping address, which you can remove from your account at any time using your dashboard. We consider your Payment Information and shipping address private and do not make such information public. To facilitate order fulfillment, we collect and store information created by your purchases made through our Services (“Transaction Data”). Transaction Data may include the merchant’s name and the date, time, and amount of the transaction.

**Advertising:** Our Services are supported by advertising. We may use the information described in this Privacy Policy to help make our advertising more relevant to you, to measure its effectiveness and to help recognize your devices to serve you ads on and off of SCN. For example, when you interact with content in the SCN for Android app, we may show content (including ads) about those same topics when you use SCN on the web. We do not use the content you share privately in Direct Messages to serve you ads. Our SCN Ads Policy also prohibits advertisers from targeting ads based on categories we consider sensitive such as race, religion, politics, sex life, or health. 

## Accessing and Modifying Your Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access, correct, delete, or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account. You can download certain account information.

You can also permanently delete your SCN account. Your account will be deactivated and then deleted. When deactivated, your account, including your name, username, and public profile, is not viewable on SCN.com. For up to 30 days after deactivation it is still possible to restore your account if it was accidentally or wrongfully deactivated. Absent a separate arrangement between you and us to extend your deactivation period, after 30 days, we begin the process of deleting your account from our systems, which can take up to a week.

Keep in mind that search engines and other third parties may still retain copies of your public information, like your user profile information even after you have deleted the information from the SCN Services or deactivated your account.
